{
  "level": "A1",
  "topic_key": "numeri",
  "topic_name": "Numeri cardinali",
  "exercises": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "9",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "2",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "18",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "9",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "10",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "13",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "8",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "17",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "14",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 14"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "20",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "5",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 5"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "1",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "8",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "6",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 6"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "6",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 6"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "4",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "12",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 12"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "15",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "18",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 18"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "2",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "2",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "7",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "7",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 7"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "12",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 12"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "3",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "9",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "16",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "5",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "5",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 5"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "6",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "15",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "7",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 7"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "11",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "18",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "15",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 15"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "3",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "6",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "6",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 6"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "8",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "16",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "8",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "14",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 14"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "14",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "20",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 20"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "20",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "20",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 20"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "2",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "2",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "12",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "12",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 12"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "11",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "1",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "15",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "15",
        "5"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "19",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "16",
        "5"
      ],
      "answer": "14",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 14"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "19"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "12",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "15",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 15"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "10",
        "19"
      ],
      "answer": "19",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 19"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "6",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "20",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "20",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 20"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "14",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "16",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "20",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 20"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "12",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "18",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 18"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "17",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "6",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 6"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "12",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "2",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "4",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "15",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "15",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "19",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "2",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "2",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "1",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "20",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 20"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "8",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "18",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "3",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "5",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 5"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "4",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "13",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "2",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "12",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "12",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 12"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "14",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "10",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "7",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "11",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "18",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 18"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "9",
        "18"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "12",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "16",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 16"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "3",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "3",
        "14"
      ],
      "answer": "14",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 14"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "12",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "12",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 12"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "6",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "17",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "10",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "16",
        "15",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "15",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 15"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "4",
        "5"
      ],
      "answer": "5",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 5"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "20",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "6",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 6"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "2",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "7",
        "5"
      ],
      "answer": "7",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 7"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "8",
        "13"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "10",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "16",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "13",
        "16"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "12",
        "18",
        "13"
      ],
      "answer": "13",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 13"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "7",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "10",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "4",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "1",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 1"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "15",
        "10"
      ],
      "answer": "10",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 10"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "18",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "8",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 8"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "9",
        "2",
        "13"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "18",
        "17"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "5",
        "4"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "8",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "15",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 15"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "9",
        "2"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "17",
        "20"
      ],
      "answer": "11",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 11"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "14",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "14",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 14"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "19",
        "3",
        "1"
      ],
      "answer": "3",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 3"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "2",
        "18",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "9",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 9"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "7",
        "15"
      ],
      "answer": "15",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 15"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "4",
        "15",
        "11"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 4"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "question": "Completa la frase: ___",
      "options": [
        "8",
        "15",
        "19"
      ],
      "answer": "19",
      "explanation": "Risposta corretta: 19"
    }
  ]
}